# 徐唯翃 William Hsu

As a psychology major, I have a solid psychology fundamental. Meanwhile, I'm preparing to get my master degree in Institute Of Communication at National Yang Ming Chiao Tung University (New Media and User Experience). On top of the psychology background, I had master UI/UX and HCI while I was at my last internship at UIUX Cafe. My specialties are to use quantitative and qualitative research to find out the mental model and the need of the user. Besides, I can draw wireframe and prototype to collect user feedback and improve the design by usability test.



Area Of Interest: Human-Computer Interaction, User Experience, Service Design



william19970923@gmail.com

# Skill

### **UI/UX** Design

- HTML
- CSS
- Adobe XD
- Framer X

## **Education**



Soochow University - Psychology

2016-2020

# **Work Experience**



### **UIUX Café - Intern**

2019.07 - 2020.06

Collaborate with Product manager, Front-end Developer and Designer. Be responsibility for planning product function with Product manager, Competitive analysis and User Research.

**Data Analysis** 

SPSS

Do prototype with Framer X by using React.js, make RWD layout by using HTML, CSS(SASS), Bootstrap and .pug.



#### Taipei Municipal Shilin Elementary School - Intern

2019.02 - 2019.06

Do case counseling and accompany, hold the consultative group with Teacher Counselor.



### **Student Sports Union - Student Reporter Intern**

2017.12 - 2018.12

Write the article of student sports competitions and assist college sports competitions conduct.